Kind Regards,

Ashiq Rahman | CEO

Logo

Web Mascot Pty Ltd
T: +1300 797 471   |   E: ashiq@webalive.com.au 
Head Office : Suite 910, 9 Yarra St, South Yarra, VIC 3141, Australia
Sydney : Level 13, 50 Carrington Street, Sydney, NSW 2000
Brisbane : Level 6, 140 Creek Street, Brisbane, QLD 4000
W: www.webalive.com.au   |  linkedin   Twitter    Blog    

This email (including all attachments) is intended solely for the named addressee. It is confidential and may contain legally privileged information. If you receive it in error, please let us know by reply email, delete it from your system and destroy any copies. This email is also subject to copyright. No part of it should be reproduced, adapted or transmitted without the written consent of the copyright owner.

Emails may be interfered with, may contain computer viruses or other defects and may not be successfully replicated on other systems. We give no warranties in relation to these matters. If you have any doubts about the authenticity of an email purportedly sent by us, please contact us immediately.